Greetz to all other respected RG's out there.Let the Legend Killing Continue...
- Morning.
- Morning, priest.
It was about 3 years ago. I was
the only kid in church that day.
The others were with Isaac
out at the cornfield.
I didn't get to go
'cause dad didn't like Isaac.
He was pretty smart, my dad.
After church we've been
to Hansen's, just like always.
Sarah was homesick with mom.
She'd turned down with a fever.
- Morning, Dave.
- Morning.
- How are your wife and Sarah?
- Dad was worried...
so he went to call mom
first thing.
- I'm gonna call your mom, ok?
- Okay!
- You want the usual?
- Yeah, strawberty shake.
That's when I saw Malachai
and the others.
I guess the meeting with Isaac
was over.
They were acting real creepy.
- There you go, Jobie.
- Thanks.
- How is she?
- I'm worried, Dave.
The fever's gone
from 101 to 104.
Sure.
Okay.
Good coffee.
Oh, my God!
No!
It happened everywhere
in Gatlin that day.
That's when Sarah started
drawing these pictures.
Happy birthday!
What are you doing?
C'mon!
Make a wish.
What did you wish for?
To live happily ever after.
- Is that a proposal?
- No, it's not.
Well, I guess I'll
give you this anyway.
What is it?
- That's nice!
- Turn it over.
In honor of this special occasion
we'll have a birthday serenade.
1, 2.
1, 2, 3, 4.
No more books and studies
Now I can stay all day
With my buddies
I can do the things I wanna do
'Cause all my exams are through
I can root for the Yankees
From the beaches
And don't have to worry
About teachers
And I'm so glad
That school is out
I could sing and shout
School is out
Everybody's gonna have some fun
Everybody's gonna jump and run
C'mon, people
Don't you be late
I just got time
To take my girl out today
You're whacko.
Holy cow!
We better get going now.
I got a lot of driving to do today.
Couldn't wejust say
the hell with it...
- and stay for a couple of hours?
- I wish.
Starting Monday I've got
fifty patients a day to look at
- I've some things you could look at.
- Is that right?
Hello?
Maid service.
We'll be out in a minute.
We gotta get going.
I'm gonna grab a quick shower
before we go, okay?
C'mon, honey! You're making
something out of nothing.
To me is something,
to you is nothing.
I'm just worried about this
internship, okay?
I've been working forthis
forfouryears.
I know.
I do understand.
Why do you have to be
such ajerk about it?
Welcome to Nebraska.
We weren't the only ones
who thought Isaac was weird.
One day Joseph told us
he was running away.
He said he couldn't
take it anymore.
He was pretty scared.
I wasn't.
- I'm scared.
- Me too.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I said I'd come back foryou.
I promise.
- Can we go with you? Please!
- No.
I'd never make it with you two.
- But we don't like it here.
- I said you'll be alright!
As long as nobody finds
that pictures you've been drawing.
She can't help it.
That won't matter
to Isaac and Malachai
They'll take it as a sign.
Anyway, you now crayons
and drawings are forbidden.
- Just like that record player.
- But we like it.
Isaac doesn't let us do anything.
Youjust better mind
until I get back.
Or else, you know what happens.
- Are you going through the corn?
- I can't go no other way.
- What if...
- I said it'll be alright.
- Unless you tell anybody I'm gone.
- We won't.
Cross your heat? Hope to die,
stick a needle in your eye.
You know what that means now?
If you tell, you're gonna burn in
a lake of fire for all eternity.
Make sure nobody's looking.
- Okay. Go!
- Nobody's looking.
I spy...
something that begins
with the letter "C".
- Corn.
- Right.
So now we know...
back roads are even less
interesting than the highways.
Maybe they've discovered music...
Hallelujah!
There are many Lord's mansions...
but there's no room
for the fornicator!
- No room!
- No room...
- for the homosexual!
- No room!
No room
for the drugs user!
No room!
Amen.
Peanut butter and white bread!
There's no room
forthe college graduated!
No room for people
who watch public television.
- No room for commitments!
- Amen!
C'mon!
Here it is.
- I wonder how it got here.
- Not me.
It looks like this one
goes to Grand Island...
and this one
cuts up to the highway.
Where's this Gatlin that we've
been seeing the signs for?
- It's not on here.
- How come? It's gotta be.
Look out!
Hang on.
Let me check.
- Where? Right there?
- Yeah.
It was just a bump.
Just tty to relax.
That was an animal, right?
I gotta go back there, okay
Just stay here and tty to rest.
C'mon, buddy.
Oh God!
- Is he...
- Oh yeah.
- Oh God!
- Easy, easy. C'mon.
Easy.
Don't look at him.
Now listen to me.
There's something vety wrong here.
So I want you to go back to the car
and wait for me there. Understand?
- And keep the doors locked.
- Why? Where are you going?
I'll tell you when I get back.
Just do what I say.
Burt.
I'm so sorty.
- Vicky, c'mon.
- Burt!
- Easy. Calm down.
- I kneeled down next to him.
It's ok. Take it easy.
Take it easy and relax.
It's okay, understand?
You're okay.
Me and Sarah were playing in our
old house. We play there lots.
Malachai said it was forbidden.
But I think that's because nobody
ever asked him to play.
When I grow up, I'm gonna have
all the money in the world.
- Me too.
- You can't.
- Why not?
- 'Cause I'm gonna have it.
- I'll get it first.
- Will not.
- Will too.
- Oh yeah? How?
Seven.
One, two, three, four,
five, six...
seven.
Alright! See?
Two hundred dollars.
No, Jobie!
How much?
- Thirteen thousand hundred dollars.
- Thirteen thousand hundred dollars?
Okay, two thousand.
I thought so.
One hundred, two hundred, three...
I gotta a great idea.
Let's pretend this guy is Isaac
and we'll put him injail.
What if he gets to get out
ofjail with a free card?
What card?
You think it might've been some
accident with farm equipment?
Not like that.
His throat was cut deliberately.
He was already dead
when he stumbled down the road.
Whoever killed him,
do you think he saw us?
- I felt like we're being watched.
- Possible.
Blood starts to coagulate
in four minutes.
When I went to get the suitcase
it was still fresh.
- He could have been out there!
- I couldn'tjust leave it there.
What if it holds
some sort of clue?
- Let's open it.
- No.
Let's just get to a phone
or a house or some place.
Malachai took us
right to Isaac.
He'd finally convinced him
punishing us for being unbelievers.
Up to them, we've been forgiven
'cause we were in the corn...
the day that "He Who Walks Behind
the Rows" made himself known.
That bothered Malachai.
He had a lot of problems.
I found these two
in one of the old homes...
they had a game, music...
and this.
They come already.
You have the gift of sight.
- This is a blessing, my child.
- I've seen this car up on the road.
Go to the old man.
Make sure he tells them nothing.
What about these two?
Take them back
where they were.
But they had a game and music.
They're forbidden.
Question me not, Malachai.
I act according to His will.
It seems we are in the Moon.
We haven't even seen a truck.
We'll be in Gatlin soon.
Do you think he lived there?
We may never knowthat.
I really thing we should open it.
Okay.
Let's see if we can get
some news.
I'm getting tired of that crap.
What is it?
- Jesus Christ!
- Not in my Book.
- It looks like primitive folk art.
- I think it's repulsive.
Sarge, bring the number six.
Damn it!
You better give me the eight.
C'mon.
We haven't got all day.
Good boy.
We'll have that transmission fixed
in no time...
then, we'll get on the radiator.
Damn. This road is becoming
a bloody highway.
I think it's the third car
in a month.
We know what to do, don't we?
We better put that suitcase away.
I'll be right back.
- Hi, we got a...
- I ain't got no gas.
- I don't need gas.
- I ain't got no diesel.
- You don't understand. I need...
- lf you don't buy gas...
you can't use the rest room.
- I need to use your phone.
- Telephone?
I ain't got no telephone.
Sarge.
Sarge, you be still.
You have to go to Hemingford.
It's about 19 miles down there.
- What about Gatlin?
- There ain't nothing in Gatlin.
What do you mean:
"There ain't nothing in Gatlin."?
Folks in Gatlin got religious.
They don't like outsiders...
and they probably won't have
a phone there either.
I'd like to stay here and talk,
but I got a transmission to fix.
If you get on that road
you'll be in Hemingford in no time.
- Right.
- Sarge, sit! At ease!
Thanks a lot.
Sarge!
Eitherthat man is senile, or he's
being out in the Sun fortoo long.
Sarge!
Come back here.
Come back here!
Under the awning!
You hear me?
Come back here.
That's an order.
Who is it?
Is that you?
What do you want?
What are you doing there?
Well, there really isn't that much
stuff in here. Just kids' stuff.
Clothes, matches,
compass, pocket knife.
- I don't get it. Camping stuff?
- Yeah.
Oh, great!
This must be our day.
In the last sign we saw
Gatlin was 3 miles...
- and pointed that way?
- That's what I thought.
- Did I miss a turn?
- No, we've been going straight.
Somebody's been
messing with the signs.
Hemingford is gotta be
straight ahead.
Must have been the wind.
These latches ain't worth a damn.
Blow all for nothing.
I nevertold them nothing.
I swear it.
I kept our bargain
just like always.
Jesus Christ! Gatlin! What do they
have? Amonopoly on road signs?
What about Hemingford?
For people who don't like visitors
they sure do advertise enough.
Overthere.
Of course, it's the wind.
Why did you have to go
afterthem, Sarge?
You bastards!
You can't do this to me.
I know you're in here.
C'mon! C'mon!
I can smell you, you stinky
little skunks.
C'mon!
Murderers little devils!
- What was that?
- Probably my golf bag.
- Are you sure?
- What do you mean: "Am I sure."?
This isn't even a road.
- We'll never gotta get out of here.
- We'll too. Stop it.
Sorty.
- Just tell me where we are.
- I don't know.
We're back where we started from.
We never should have listen
to that old fool.
Hemingford is 19 miles,
Gatlin is only 3.
I don't care how much religious
they've got. We're going there.
Don't ever show up
in my emergency room, buddy.
Behold.
Adream did come to me in the
night. And the Lord show all to me.
Praise God!
Praise the Lord.
Atime of tribulation has come.
Atest is at hand.
- The final test.
- What has the Lord commanded?
In the dream...
the Lord did come to me
and he was a shape.
It was He Who Walks
Behind The Rows.
And I did fall on my knees
in terror and hide my eyes...
unless the fierceness of His face
struck me dead.
He told me all
that it since happened.
He said:"Joseph has taken his
things and fled this happy place...
because the worship of me
is no more upon him...
so take you his life
and spill his blood".
- He did?
- Yes.
"But let not the flesh
pollute the corn.
- Cast him instead upon the road."
- And so was done.
Joseph, the betrayer,
was cast out.
And He Who Walks
Behind the Rows did say...
"I will send outlanders
amongst you.
Aman and a woman.
And these outlanders...
will be unbelievers
and profaners of the holy".
- I thought Isaac never came here.
- But he's always been here.
Just like He Who Walks
Behind The Rows.
"And the man shall
sorely test you...
for He has great power. Even
greaterthan that of the blue man.
The blue man!
Yes, the blue man!
And just as the blue man
was offered upon to Him...
- so shall be the unbelievers!
- Make sacrifice unto Him.
Bring the blood
of the outlanders.
Praise God!
Praise The Lord!
Let's get out of here!
Praise God!
Praise The Lord!
It looks like a swinging place.
I guess nobody told them
we were coming.
I hope not.
I don't see anybody.
Town Hall.
Grocety store. Hansen's Cafe.
It seems they got a phone.
Unless a ghost is using it.
- What is it with this corn?
- You got me.
Is dead.
Just like evetything else here.
- A rat.
- Yeah. Just an ordinaty rat.
Now can we
get out of here, please?
Wait a minute!
Come back here!
C'mon, Vicky. Hurty up.
I don't wanna lose them.
What are you gonna do
if you catch them?
Ask where we can get help.
What else?
They just got off that way.
Damn!
Where did they go?
We're already in the car. Why
wouldn't wejust go to Hemingford?
- That would take us 20 minutes.
- We'd just found people.
Yeah, three kids
that tried to steal our car.
There's something
vety strange about this town.
We'd be better off
in a biggertown anyway.
- The size of Seattle.
- Yeah.
- Overthere!
- What?
- I just saw a door open and close.
- I didn't see anything.
- Let's check it out.
- Why? I thought we were going.
- Settle down.
- Don't patronize me.
I'm not patronizing you. I just
wanna see if there's someone there.
Hello?
Anybody home?
We've had an accident.
We need to use your phone.
Okay.
Now can we go?
- Burt, this is somebody's house.
- I know. I just want a phone.
Hello?
Gross.
I'll check out the back.
I found the phone.
Matches the decor.
This is three years old.
I don't understand
what's going on here.
Well, can we go?
Burt!
Hello?
Anybody here?
Don't be afraid.
We didn't mean to scare you.
Hi!
- What's your name?
- Sarah.
Sarah!
That's a beautiful name.
- This is Burt and I'm Vicky.
- Are you here alone, Sarah?
Do you live here?
Youjust come here to play?
- Are your mommy and daddy around?
- They're in the corn field.
- What are they doing there?
- All the grown ups are there.
Are they working there
or having a meeting?
No. Isaac put them there.
Who's Isaac?
- Sweetheart, tell us who Isaac is.
- Our leader.
Leader of what?
Evetybody.
Of course.
Listen,
could you take us to Isaac?
- Why not?
- He's scaty.
It's vety important we speak to
some grown ups as soon as possible.
- We're wasting ourtime, Vicky.
- Give her a chance.
I'm gonna go look
at the Town Hall.
Why?
Because we have a murder
to report...
and we're walking in circles,
wasting ourtime.
- Maybe she can help.
- Fine. You stay here with her.
Things aren't happening fast.
I'm gonna leave you the car.
I won't be gone vety long.
If anybody comes, honk. Okay?
Are we safe?
Yes. It's weird here,
but it's safe.
I'll be back.
So, it looks like it's just
you and me.
What were you doing here
by yourself? Just playing records?
Come on, you can tell me.
Drawing.
Drawing...
- what's so secret about drawing?
- I'm not supposed to.
You're not supposed to draw?
- Who says? Isaac?
- Malachai.
Malachai?
Why don't you draw me a picture
we won't tell Isaac...
or Malachai
or anybody?
- How's that sound?
- Okay.
- How's it coming?
- Fine.
- What did you draw?
- You.
You did?
Can I see?
What is this?
Burt?
Burt, is that you?
Somebody here?
Who are you?
What do you want?
We want to give you peace.
Seize her.
Come on! Get her!
Let's finish it!
No!
Burt!
- Are we safe?
- Yes, it's weird here, but it's safe.
Help me!
Where are you taking me?
Help!
Vicky!
Sarah, what happened here?
What happened?
Where's Vicky?
You've gotta think.
Think.
What happened to her?
Please!
Does He speak to you, Isaac?
He speaks to me always.
But today he's displeased.
He's displeased with you,
Malachai.
What have I done?
Question Him not in vain.
Do you not know you sacrificed
Joseph without an offering?
And did you not spill the blood
of the old man...
when his oil and gasoline
were still useful to us?
We have our own fuel now
from the corn.
Sow not your pride, Malachai.
We have not enough.
Maybe He's displeased
that we have not offered Him...
- Sarah and Jobe.
- Sarah has the gift of sight.
She warned us of the coming
of the interlopers.
Question not my judgment,
Malachai.
I am the giver of His word.
Go you and bring me the husband.
We must offerthem tonight
when Amos leaves.
Sarah, come on.
Tell me what happened to her.
Look at me!
Think!
- What?
- Malachai.
Who's Malachai?
What do you mean?
Vicky?
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Nowthe blood of Amos
will be shared.
Stop it!
Stop that!
Hold the outlander!
What the hell is going on here?
Are you crazy?
What do you think you're doing?
My passage.
It's my birthday.
You've got a pretty sick way
of celebrating it, pal.
Silence, interloper!
Your presence profanes
this holy place.
- He will wreck with you.
- Great. I don't know who He is.
Maybe He'd like to discuss
what's going on here with me.
- It says it should be...
- Amos!
- It says it is written.
- Speak no more to him!
He is an unbeliever.
Hurty, get Isaac!
No! Wait!
Bring Malachai.
What do you mean: "As it's
written? "Written where?
What? In this?
Are you rewriting the whole thing
orthe parts that suit your needs?
- Back off!
- Sit down!
What do we have here?
Nineteen, eighteen...
What is this?
- These people died so young!
- Not died.
We go to Him the first night
of our nineteenth year.
Who the hell is Him?
He Who Walks
Behind The Rows.
Malachai comes!
Seize him!
Back off!
Seize him.
Do not let him escape.
Where is he?
Come on!
There he is. Go get him!
You! Go that way!
I need your help!
Come on!
Come on, help me
Help me!
Outlander!
He's here.
- Got you.
- This isn't a game.
Back off!
Outlander!
Go get him!
Check the doors!
You guys go back to the alley.
You, overthere. You two follow me.
Shit!
Damn it!
Hey, mister!
I know a place to hide.
But we gotta hurty.
- Who are you?
- Jobe. Stop asking questions.
Come on!
Will you come on?
Careful.
Don't be a scared cat.
- Come on. It's only me and Sarah.
- Sarah?
Yes, my sister.
Isn't that nice?
My dad built it...
when the communists launched
theirfirst strike.
I don't think it's the communists
we have to worty about.
Don't worty.
Nobody knows about this place.
It's secret.
- Those guys are friends of yours?
- No way!
They listen to Isaac
and Malachai.
- Who are Isaac and Malachai?
- Isaac started the whole thing.
If he hadn't come,
this would never have happened.
When he was young,
he was a preacher...
so evetybody believed him.
They thought he had
a great spirit.
I thought he was weird.
We must sacrifice
them both tonight.
Amos will satisfy Him.
We need the woman.
- She'll bring the man to us.
- No.
He must be taken
without her.
We cannot remove her
from this place. It is holy.
We'll bring the Lord two
by using one.
Do not blaspheme, Malachai.
You know not the laws.
He speaks them only to me.
I think not, Isaac.
You are the one who's lost
favor with Him.
He's a God of blood
and sacrifice, not ceremonies.
Sacrilege!
Down on your knees, heretic!
Shut your mouth, Isaac!
You've grown proud farfrom us.
He Who Walks Behind The Rows
will decide yourfate.
Don't you sit there, seize him!
Punish him, cut him down.
I command you!
I am the word and the giver
of His laws.
Disobedience to me
is disobedience to Him.
Do it now oryour punishment
will be a thousand times...
a thousand deaths, each more
horrible than the last.
They're tired of yourtalk.
I've showed them what I can do.
Cut the woman down.
Put Isaac in her place.
We'll see howthe Lord
favors you.
Dare not to blaspheme.
He will punish you.
The God of hell will devouryou.
All of you!
No! No!
When my dad wouldn't get up
I ran from Hansen...
to get Officer Hodgekiss.
But it was too late.
Why?
What happened to him?
He got away at that time.
He went to the barn
after he talked to the minister.
Minister?
- What happened to the minister?
- Malachai.
Outlander!
You, overthere.
He's coming.
Outlander!
We have your woman.
She still lives.
Outlander!
Maybe you don't hear so well.
Her blood will spill
unless you give yourself up.
We won't wait much longer.
The night is coming.
Night is His time.
Outlander!
Come on!
Come on, outlander!
Are you looking forthat lady?
- Yes, you know where she is?
- They took her out to the clearing.
- What clearing? Where?
- In the corn field.
- Are you sure?
- Of course I'm sure.
I followed them,
just like I followed you.
Show me.
- Okay.
- Come on, let's go.
Okay.
Quiet.
Come on.
Follow me to the barn.
Careful.
I'm ready to celebrate
my birthday.
Malachai!
He will not forgive you.
None of you will be forgiven.
All of you shall feel His wrath!
We have a surprise foryou,
Amos.
Isaac is gonna keep you company.
I am the word
and the giver of His laws.
This is the end!
Come on.
Over here.
You can see evetything from here.
Okay, you two...
you stay here and wait for me.
All right?
But if anything happens to me...
you get to Hemingford
as fast as you can.
You get on that road
and don't get off it. Understand?
Go past the irrigation pump.
It's Him.
He's come for me.
He's come to welcome me.
I'm here, Lord.
I'm ready.
Take me now, Lord.
Your will, Lord.
My passage.
I did it right.
I swear it.
I did evetything You wanted!
No! No!
Stop!
Vicky, come on,
run to the barn!
He hit Malachai!
- Seize him.
- Take that.
Vicky, get out of here!
Was it like that with your
parents? Was it?
Just because some suck
proclaims himself a holy man...
and says God commands?
What kind of God tells children
to kill their parents?
Answer me that, buddy.
Did you hearthat
before Isaac? Did you?
I can't believe
you're this blind.
Maybe you've been listening
to this holy roller so long...
that all starts to sound the same.
But it's not!
Any religion without love
and compassion is false.
It's a lie!
Is he dead?
Is this what you want?
Is it what He commands?
I don't think so.
Get him!
Stop him!
Kill him!
Malachai!
He wants you too, Malachai.
He wants you too.
- Vicky?
- Burt? Over here!
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Get down.
Get some help and get
those doors closed. Quick.
Rudolf, Robert, come on!
- What do we do?
- I don't know.
If I knew what it was,
I could tell you.
It's He Who Walks
Behind The Rows.
What if we tried to make it
to the road?
I think we're safer here,
for now.
Has anybody evertried
to hurt the monster?
Any of the adults, your parents
before they were killed?
The Blue Man!
Who is the Blue Man?
What did he do?
Officer Hodgekiss.
I told you.
He came down here
after he talked to the minister.
He was reading a page
torn out from the Bible...
and it was working
with distil.
What was he reading
at the Bible?
What was it?
Do you know?
You have it?
Hurty up. Where is it?
"And the devil
that deceived them...
was cast into the lake of fire
and sulphur.
Where the beast and the false
prophet shall be tormented...
day and night,
for ever and ever."
What's that supposed to mean?
What was the Blue Man
doing at the distil?
He hooked the hose
and he was ttying to roll it out.
- What stopped him?
- Malachai.
Lake of fire. Fire!
He was gonna burn the field.
Oh, yes.
The alcohol from the distil.
- How?
- Never mind, never mind.
Kids, you bring me as many hoses
as you can find. Quick!
Jobie and Sarah. Find me a bottle.
Aglass bottle.
Quick!
Move!
Vicky, come here!
Over here!
It doesn't fit.
There's gotta be a connector
here somewhere.
Tty this.
Get somebody
to hold this on tight.
- Okay.
- Hang on to it. You got one. Good!
Vicky, see if you can find me
a thick rag.
Jobie, come here.
Hey, this is not a rag.
Get them to hold on that tight.
Open it up when I get there.
All right?
All right.
Be careful.
I love you, Vicky.
What are you doing here?
Get back to the barn.
Hurty up!
Go on!
Move! Now!
Excuse me!
Get that valve. Quick.
Do you know howto run
this thing?
- Crank it!
- What?
Crank it.
Push the button at the top.
Now!
- Get the bottle!
- Okay!
Jobie!
Come back here!
Run, come on, run!
- Jobie!
- Here's the bottle!
Throw it!
It's the right time!
Burt!
Jobie!
- Vicky!
- Sarah!
Jobie!
Look!
Come on! Come on!
Let's go!
- Is he dead?
- I think so.
Then why are we still running?
- Just keep going!
- Where did you get this guy?
Hemingford is 19 miles
right?
- We'll walk?
- Sure.
Are you sure
you're strong enough?
I'm okay. And you?
Are you okay?
I'll make it.
I got a great doctor.
Jealous?
So what do we do with these
two little kids?
I don't know.
You guys wanna stay with us
for a couple of days?
How about a week?
Okay.
- How about a month?
- No.
All right. All right.
I'll grab the map.
- Interloper! No!
- God!
You must die!
Oh, boy!
She's out cold.
What are we gonna do now?
Send her a card from Seattle.
Let's get out of here.
内布拉斯加州 盖特林镇
三年前
-早
-早,牧师
那大约是在三年前
那天我是去教堂的唯一的孩子
其他的孩子跟 lsaac 去了玉米田
我没有去是因为爸爸不喜欢 lsaac
我爸爸他非常聪明
做完礼拜, 我们去 Hansen 家
像往常一样
Sarah 和妈妈在一起
她想家了
结果发烧病倒了
早,Dave.
- 早, Pop
- 你妻子和 Sarah 怎么样了?
爸爸有点担心,所以他早上就去打电话给妈妈
我去打电话给你妈妈,OK?
OK
- OK,Joby,老样子吗?
- 是的,要草莓奶昔
就在那时我看到 Malachai 和其他孩子
我猜跟 Isaac 的聚会结束了
他们的样子看起来真阴森
- 这个给你,Joby
- 哦,谢谢
她怎样?
我很担心,Dave
已经从101度 烧到 104度 了
好的
咖啡很好喝
那天在盖特森镇到处都发生了这样的事
也是从那时开始
Sarah 开始画这些画的
生日快乐
你在做什么?
许个愿吧
你许了什么愿?
永远幸福的生活
那是在求婚吗?
不…不是
不管怎样
我想我还是要把这个送给你
是什么
哦,真漂亮
翻到背面
- ( chuckles )
- ( giggIes )
l like this.
为纪念这一特别的日子
我们来听一首生日小夜曲
不用再看书学习
现在我能整天和伙伴们待在一起
我能做我想做的事
因为所有的考试都已结束
我可以在海滩为洋基队喝彩
不用再担心老师
我真高兴学期已经结束
我可以欢歌高呼
学期已经结束,每个人都能痛快玩耍
每个人都能雀跃奔跑
来吧 朋友 别迟了
我今天正有时间带我的姑娘出去
你真是疯子
Holy cow!
我们现在最好走了.
我今天要开很长的路呢
我们不能就说,"让它见鬼去吧"?
- 然后在这儿待几小时呢?
- 我也希望
从周一起,
我每天要去看50个病人
我有些东西你可以看看
是吗?
Hello?Hello?客房服务
我们马上出来
哦,我们得走了
趁走之前这点时间我先冲个凉,OK?
别这样,亲爱的,你在小事化大
对我而言这是大事,对你而言是小事
我只是比较担心这个实习期,OK?
我为这个机会付出了四年的努力
我知道
我真的明白
只是你干嘛为这事这么神经呢?
"欢迎来到内布拉斯加州"
我们并不是唯一觉得 lsaac 很古怪的人
一天 Joseph 告诉我们他要逃跑
他说他再也受不了他了
他很害怕,但我不害怕
- 我害怕
- 我也是
没什么可害怕的
我说了我会回来找你们的
我保证
- 我们能跟你一起吗?求你!
- 不
带着你们两个我就没法成功了
- 但我们不喜欢这里
- 我说了你们不会有事的
只要没人发现你画的那些画
她也阻止不了自己画画
lsaac 和 Malachai 不会管
他们会把它当作一种预兆
总之,蜡笔和画画是被禁止的
就像那个唱机一样
但我们喜欢它.
lsaac 什么也不准我们做!
你们最好听话,等到我回来
不然你们知道会发生什么
你要从玉米田穿过去吗?
- 我没有其他路可以走
- 但要是...
我说了不会有事的
除非你们告诉别人我走了
- 我们不会的
- 你能发誓吗?如果泄露...?
就会被针刺穿眼睛而死
OK,你们现在明白了吗?
如果说出去,你们就会被火湖燃烧,万劫不复!
去侦查一下确保没人看见
OK!走吧!
没人在看,没人在看
我看见两边是...
字母"C"开头的东西
- 玉米
- 答对了
那么现在我们知道了...
抄近路比走公路更无聊
或许这样人们才发明了音乐
哈利路亚
上帝的国度有许多地方
但没有地方能容得下通奸者!
- 没有地方!
- 没地方能容得下...
- 同性恋!
- 没有地方!
- 没有地方能容得下瘾君子!
阿门!花生酱加白面包
没有地方能容得下大学毕业生
没有地方能容得下看公共电视台的人
- 没有地方能容得下婚姻的承诺!
- 阿门!
别这样
在这儿
不知道谁放在这儿的
不是我
看起来这条路是通往格兰德岛的
而这可以转到公路
我们看到路标上标的这个叫
盖特林的镇在哪儿呢?
这上面没有
怎么会?
应该有啊
小心
等下
让我看看.
- 哪儿,这里?
- 是的
只是有点肿了
别紧张,放松下
那是头动物,对吗?
我得回去看看,OK?
你待在车里休息一下
来,朋友
他是不是...
哦,是的
- 哦,上帝!
- 放松,放松,好了
放松
别看他
OK,现在听我说
这里看起来好像很不对劲
所以我要你回到车里,在那等我
明白吗?并且把车门锁好
- 为什么?你要去哪儿?
- 我回来后会告诉你的
总之照我说的做
Burt?
Burt?!
我真的很抱歉
- Vicky,醒醒
- Burt!
- 放松,冷静
- 我刚才...
我刚才在他身边跪下...
没事,别紧张
冷静点,放松
没事的,明白吗?
- 是的
- 你没事
我和 Sarah 在我们的老房子里玩
我们常在那里玩
MaIachai 说那是禁止的
但我想那是因为从没有人邀请他玩
等我长大后
我会拥有世界上所有的钱
我也会
- 你不能
- 为何不能?
- 因为它们会是我的
- 我会先得到
- 不会
- 会
- 会的!
哦,是吗?怎么得到?
7.
1 2 3 4 5
6...
7.
太好了,看到吗?
两百美元
不对,Joby
多少?
1300000美元
1300000美元?
好吧,200000
我想也是
一百,二百,三…
我想到个好主意
我们假装这个家伙是 lsaac
我们把他关进监狱
如果他用"出狱卡"从监狱出来了呢?
什么卡?
你觉得会不会是农场上什么设备出了故障了?
不像是
他的喉咙是被人故意割的
他在摇摇晃晃走到路上前就已经死了
无论是谁杀死他的--
你觉得那人看到我们了吗?
我是说,我感觉我们好像在被监视
可能吧
血液会在四分钟后凝结
当我去拿手提箱时
它还没有凝结
- 那他可能就在那
- 我不能把手提箱就那样留在那
如果里面能找到什么线索呢?
- 让我们打开它
- 不
我们还是去找一部电话
或找到所房子或是什么地方吧
Malachai 直接把我们带去见 Isaac
他最终想说服他惩罚我们这些背叛者
对于他们,本来已原谅了我们
因为"走在玉米田后者"出现的那天
我们也在玉米地里
那令 Malachai 觉得不安
他有着很多问题
我在一个老房子里找到这两个小家伙
他们在玩游戏 听音乐
还有这个
他们已经来了
你有天眼
这是天赐,我的孩子
我在路上看到了这辆车
去找那老头
确保他不会告诉他们任何事
那这两个怎么办?
带他们回他们原来的地方
但他们刚才玩游戏听音乐了
- 那是禁止的!
- 别质疑我,Malachai
我是依它的旨意行事
我们好像在月球上似的
我们连一辆车也没看见
我们很快就到盖特林了
你觉得他住在那么?
我们也许永远不会知道
我真的觉得我们该打开那箱子
好吧
让我们听听有没有什么新闻
我受够了这些狗屁
什么?
- 老天啊
- 不是在我书里的
看起来像是什么原始的民间艺术品
我觉得它很恶心
Sarge,把6号拿来
该死
最好还是给我8号
快点,快点
我们可没一整天时间
好孩子,Sarge
我们很快就会修好变速器!
然后我们再修水箱
见鬼,这条小路变成他妈的公路了
我想这是一个月里第三辆车了,是不是?
我们知道要怎么做,对吗?
我们最好把手提箱藏起来
我就回来
- 嗨,我们…
- 我没有汽油
- 不,我不需要汽油
- 我也没有柴油
你不明白,我需要--
如果你不是要买油
你就不能用厕所
我是需要用你的电话
电话?!
我没有电话
Sarge
Sarge,你安静待着
你应该去海明福特
- 那大概离这儿有19英里
- 那么盖特林镇在哪?
盖特林?那里什么都没有
"盖特林那里什么都没有"
这话什么意思?
盖特林镇上的人是信徒
他们不喜欢外来者
他们那儿应该也不会有电话
Sarge!先生,我也想在这儿跟你聊聊
但我还得去修变速器,
如果你从那条路走
你很快就能到海明福特的
好吧
Sarge
坐下,安静!
多谢
Sarge!
那人要么是因为年纪大了
要么就是在太阳底下晒太久了
Sarge!
给我回来
Sarge,给我回来!
到遮篷下去
听见没?
给我回来
回来.
这是命令!
是谁?
是你吗?
你想要什么?
你在那里做什么?
这里真的没什么,就是些小孩的东西--
衣服、火柴、指南针、小折刀
- 我不明白,只有些野营用的东西?
- 是的
哦,好极了
今天是什么日子啊
我们最后看到的一个路标写着
"盖特林镇还有三英里"
- 而且是指向那的?
- 我也这么记得
我是不是漏掉一个转弯了?
不是,我们一直在笔直开
一定有人对路标做了手脚
- 海明福特应该就在前头
- 是的
可能是风吹的吧
这些门真没用
一点风都经不住
我什么也没告诉他们
我发誓.
我一如既往遵守我们的协议
老天啊!盖特林镇!
他们到底做了什么?垄断了所有路标吗?
那么海明福特在哪?
既然他们不喜欢外来者,
那他们做的广告似乎过多了
往那儿
当然,是风干的
你为什么非要去追他们呢,Sarge?
你们这些杂种
你们不能这么对我
我知道你在这里
出来
出来!
我能闻到你,
你们这些发臭的小杂种
出来!
杀人犯小魔鬼!
那是什么?
可能是我的高尔夫球棒
- 你确定吗?
- 什么意思,我确定吗?
上帝,这甚至不是公路
- 我们永远出不去了
- 我们可以,住嘴!
对不起
- 告诉我我们在哪
- 我也不知道
我们又回到原来的地方了
我们真不该听那老糊涂的话
海明福特有19英里远,
盖特林镇才3英里
我不管他们信什么教
我们就去那
别让我在我的急诊室看见你,伙计
听着
上帝昨晚托给我一个梦
向我展示了一切
赞美上帝
赞美主
磨难的时刻到来了
考验降临了
- 最终的考验
- 上帝有什么指示?
在梦中,
上帝确实降临在我面前
真实地出现
它就是"走在玉米田后者"
而我敬畏地双膝下跪
遮住我的眼睛
直到它狂怒的脸
令我有如死的感觉
自从一切发生时
它已告诉了我所有事
他说：
"Joseph 已经带着他的东西
要逃离这片快乐之地
"因为他已不再信奉我
"所以你必须让他的生命结束
让他的血流干"
- 他那么干了?
- 是的
"但别让他的肉体污染了这片玉米田
- "必须把他丢弃在路上"
- 已经奉旨行事!
Joseph 这个背叛者已被驱逐出去
"走在玉米田后者"又说：
"我会派外来者到你们中间
"一个男人和一个女人
"而这些外来者
会是背叛和亵渎圣灵的人"
我以为 Isaac never 从不来这儿
但他一直在这里
就像"走在玉米田后者"一样
"而这个人会痛苦得考验你们
"因为他有强大的力量
"甚至比那个蓝人更强大!"
蓝人
是的,蓝人
就像蓝人已被献祭给它一样
背叛者都将被献祭
给它准备祭品
把外来者的血带来给它
赞美上帝
赞美主
让我们离开这儿
这地方看起来真是一片死寂
我猜没人告诉他们我们来了吧
我希望不是
上帝,我没看到任何人
市政厅
杂货店
Hansen咖啡馆
看起来他们好像有电话,是不?
除非是鬼魂使用的
这些玉米是怎么回事?
你把我问倒了
这是坏的
就像这里的所有东西一样
- 一只老鼠
- 是的
只是只普通的老鼠
我们现在能出去了吗?
嘿嘿,等一下,回来
快来,Vicky.
快点,我不想让他们跑了
你追到他们想怎么做?
问问我们到哪能求助啊,还能做什么?
他们从那跑了
见鬼!他们去哪了?
听着,我们已经上车了
何不干脆去海明福特呢?
用20分钟就到了
我们刚看到人了
是啊,企图偷我们车的三个毛孩子
这个镇看起来很怪异
也许你说得对
要是我们在一个大点儿的城市就会好许多
- 比如西雅图那样大的
- 是啊
- 那边
- 什么?
我看到一扇开着的门关上了
我什么也没看见
让我们去看看
为什么?我们不是要离开吗?
冷静点
- 别高人一等的样子
- 我没高人一等的样子
我只是想看看那里面是否有人
有人在家吗?
我们出了点问题
想借用下电话
行了吗?
现在我们能走了吗?
Burt,这是别人的家
我知道,我只是用下电话而已
真恶心
我去后面看看
我找到电话了
跟房间的装饰还真配
这个是三年前的了
我不明白这里是怎么回事
好了,我们能走了吗?
这里有人吗?
别害怕,我们无意吓着你的
- 你叫什么名字?
- Sarah
哦,Sarah.
一个好听的名字
他是 Burt
我叫 Vicky
你一个人在这儿吗,Sarah?
你住在这儿吗?
你只是来这儿玩的?
你妈妈爸爸在附近吗?
他们在玉米田里
他们在那里做什么?
所有的大人们都在那儿
他们是在那儿干活
还是有什么聚会?
不是,lsaac 让他们在那儿的
谁是 lsaac?
宝贝,告诉我们 Isaac 是谁
我们的领导
领导什么?
所有人
当然
听着, 你能带我们去找 lsaac 吗?
为何不能?
他很吓人
听着,Sarah,
我们急需尽快找到一个大人谈谈
我们在浪费时间,Vicky
给她个机会嘛
我要去那市政厅看看
为什么?
因为我们有一宗谋杀案要报告
而我们却在这里转圈,浪费时间
也许她能帮助我们
也好,那你留在这儿跟她说
听着,我们进展的太慢了
我把车留下给你
我不会去很久
如果有人来,你就按喇叭,好吗?
我们会安全吗?
会的,虽然这里有点怪
但应该是安全的
我很快回来
那么…看起来现在只有你和我了
你一个人在这里做什么?
只是在放唱片?
来嘛,你可以告诉我
- 画画
画画干嘛要偷偷摸摸的呢?
因为我不可以画画
你不可以画画?
谁说的?Isaac?
Malachai
Malachai?
这样吧,你给我画一张画好吗
我们不告诉 Isaac 或 Malachai 或任何人
- 怎么样?
- 好的
- 画得怎样了?
- 好了
- 你话了什么?
- 你
是吗?
我能看看吗?
这是什么?
Burt?
Burt,是你吗?
有人在这儿吗?
你是谁?
你们想做什么?
我们要给你平静
抓住她
快点!抓住她
"我们会安全吗?"
"会的,虽然这里有点怪,但应该是安全的"
救我
你们要带我去哪儿?
Burt!
Vicky!
Sarah,这里发生了什么?
发生了什么?
Vicky 在哪儿?
你得想一下
想想
她发生什么事了?求你!
它跟你说话了吗,Isaac?
它一直跟我说话
但今天它很不满
它对你很不满,Malachai
我做了什么?
不要轻慢地质疑它
你难道不知道
你杀了 Joseph 但没有拿来献祭?
你还杀死了那老头
在他的汽油还对我们有用的时候
难道不是吗?
我们现在能从玉米田获得我们所需的燃料
勿狂妄自大,Malachai.
我们的燃料还不够
也许它不满是因为
我们没献祭给它 Sarah 和 Job
Sarah 有天眼
是她提醒了我们闯入者的到来
不要质疑我的判断,MaIachai
我是它的旨意的传达者
你们去把她丈夫给我带来
我们必须在今晚 Amos 离开时
把他们作为献祭
Sarah,快点.
告诉我她发生什么事了
Sarah,看着我
想想啊
- Malachai
- 什么?
- MaIachai
- 谁是 Malachai?什么意思?
Vicky?
杀 杀 杀 杀 杀...
(并且一个孩子须领导他们)
现在让我们一起分享 Amos 的血!
停下!停下!
- 怎么了?
- 拦住外来者!
这里到底发生了什么?
你疯了吗?
你到底以为自己在做什么?
我将离去,
今天是我的生日
你庆祝生日的方式真变态,朋友
- 听着,我…
- 安静,闯入者!
你的出现亵渎了这片神圣的地方
他会破坏它的事
很好,我不知道这个他是谁
按也许他愿意和我谈谈这里到底发生了什么事
- 上面说应该…
- Amos!
这是根据上面所写的
别再跟他说话了!
他是背叛者,快,去找 lsaac
不,等等
去找 Malachai 来
你说"这是根据上面所写的"是什么意思?
哪里所写的?
怎么,这上面的吗?
你把整本《圣经》都改写了
还是只是其中满足你们需要的部分?
退后
坐下
这里都是些什么?
19,18--
这是什么?
这些人都这么年轻就死去
不是死,我们在…
我们第19年的第一个夜晚将去找它
它到底是谁?
"走在玉米田后者"
Malachai 来了!
抓住他
退后!
抓住他,别让他跑了
他在那儿,去抓住他
你们!去那边!
我需要帮助
快点!
帮帮我,帮帮我!
外来者!
他在这儿!
- 抓到你了
- 这不是在玩游戏
退后
外来者
去抓住他!
去门那儿看看
你们到小巷里看看
你,去那儿
你们俩跟我来
妈的
嘿,先生
我知道一个地方可以藏身
但我们得快点
- 你是谁?
- Job
快点.
别问问题了
快点
你快点好不好?
小心点
嘿,别像只受惊吓的小猫似的
- 来吧.这里只有我跟 Sarah
- Sarah?
是啊,我妹妹
不错吧?
这是我爸爸造的
在共产主义者发动第一次攻击时
我想我们要担心的不是什么共产主义者
不用担心
没人知道这个地方
这是个秘密
- 那些人是你们的朋友吗?
- 当然不是
他们听命于 lsaac 和 MaIachai
lsaac 和 Malachai 是谁?
是 lsaac 挑起的这一切
如果没有他来
这一切都不会发生
但在他小时候,他是个传教者
所以每个人都相信他
他们认为他有伟大的灵魂
我觉得他很古怪,对吗, Sarah?
我们今晚要把他们两个献祭
Amos 会让它满意了
我们需要留着这女人
她能让那个男人来找我们
不,我们不需要用她来抓住他
我们不能让她离开这里
这里是神圣的
我们可以利用一个换来两个
献给上帝
别亵渎神明,MaIachai!
你不知道它的法律.
它只告诉我
我不认为,Isaac.
失去它的宠爱的人是你
它是血和献祭之神
不是仪式之神
亵渎神明!
给我跪下,异教徒!
闭上你的嘴,lsaac
你狂妄的已经眼里没有我们了
"走在玉米田后者"会决定你的命运
你们别再坐着了,抓住他!
惩罚他!
砍死他!我命令你们!
我是它的法律和旨意的传达者
对我不从就是对它不从
马上行动
否则你们将受到一千倍的惩罚
一千次的死
一次比一次更可怕
我们听够了你的屁话,lsaac
我已经让他们看到了我能做什么
把那女人放下来
让 lsaac 替她
让我们看看上帝是怎么宠幸你的
不,你敢亵渎神明
他会惩罚你的
地狱之神会吞噬你
你们所有人!不!
当我爸爸无法站起来时…
我从 Hansen 的咖啡馆跑出去找
Hotchkiss 警官
但已经太迟了
为何,他发生什么事了?
他那时已经离开了
他在跟牧师谈过话后
就去了谷仓
牧师?
牧师发生什么了?
Malachai…
外来者!
你们,去那儿
- 你跟我去这条街
- 外来者!
外来者!
你的女人在我们这儿
她还活着
外来者,也许你还听不大见吧
外来者,如果你不出来投降
我们就给她放血了
我们不会等太久的
夜晚就要降临了
今晚它的时间就到了
外来者!
出来!
出来,外来者!
外来者!
你是在找那位小姐吗?
是的,你是到她在哪吗?
- 他们带她到空地去了
- 什么空地?在哪儿?
在玉米田里
- 你确定吗?
- 我当然确定
- 我跟踪他们了,就像我跟踪你一样
- 带我去
- 好吧
- 来吧,我们走
好的
安静
来吧
跟我去谷仓
小心
我们已经准备好庆祝我的生日了
Malachai,它不会原谅你的!
你们都不会得到原谅!
他的愤怒会降临到你们所有人头上!
我们有个惊喜给你,Amos
lsaac 将会与你作伴
我是他的法律和旨意的传达者!
这一切要结束了!
来吧
在这儿
你从这儿能看到一切
OK,你们两个…
你们待在这里等我,好吗?
但如果我发生什么事…
你们就尽快赶去海明福特
你们上了那条路就千万别回头,明白吗?
知道了
走过那个灌溉水泵
是他
他来找我了
他是来欢迎我的
我在这儿,上帝!
带我走吧,上帝!
你的意愿,上帝!
你的旨意
我是按你的旨意做的
我发誓
我一切都是如你的意愿所做
不
不!
Boy:
lt's the outlander!
快点,走.
去谷仓
Vicky,离开这里
你们也是这样对你们父母的,是吗?
就因为一个骗子自称自己是圣徒…
并说这是上帝的旨意吗?
什么样的上帝会要孩子杀死自己的父母?
回答我,伙计
在 lsaac 出现前你们听说过这儿吗?
有吗?
我真不敢相信你们就是群瞎子
也许你们听这"神圣的骗子"的话听得太久了
所以所有人说的听起来都一样
但根本不是这样!
任何没有爱和怜悯的信仰
都是虚假的
这是个谎言
这就是你们想要的吗?
这就是他的命令吗?
我不认为是
抓住他
拦住他
杀死他
MaIachai!
他也许想带走你...
Malachai!
他也要带走你
- Vicky?
- Burt?
在这里,你受伤了
- 你还好吧?
- 还好
低下头
Joby,去找人帮忙
还有把门关上,快!
- Peter,Robert,快来
- 我们怎么做?
我不知道
如果我知道那是什么
我就告诉你了
他是"走在玉米田后者"
如果我们想办法到那条路上去呢?
我想暂时来说
我们待在这里安全
Joby,有没有人曾试过攻击那魔鬼?
任何大人,你们的父母?
在他们被杀前曾试过吗?
蓝人
蓝人是谁?
他怎么做的?
是 Hotchkiss 警官
我跟你说过的
在他跟牧师谈过后
就来了这里
他读到了圣经上撕下来的一页
- 说是需要用蒸馏器
- 等一下
他在圣经上读到什么?
是什么?
你知道吗?
你有它吗?
快点,他在哪里?
"那迷惑他们的魔鬼
"被扔在硫磺的火湖里
"就是野兽和假先知所在的地方
"他们必昼夜受痛苦,直到永永远远"
这到底是什么意思?
Job,蓝人用蒸馏器做什么?
他接上了管子
然后把它延伸出去
- 那是什么阻止了他?
- MaIachai
"火湖",火!
他是要烧掉玉米田
哦,对了
酒精.蒸馏器
- 怎么做?
- 没关系,不用管了
孩子们,你们去找管子来给我
有多少要多少,快!
Job 和 Sarah,
给我找一个瓶子,玻璃瓶
快,去吧
Vicky,过来
对不上
这里应该有个连接管的
试试这个
找个人来抓紧这个
- 好的!
- 抓紧他
你找到了一个,很好
Vicky,去看看能不能给我找块厚点的破布
Joby,过来
嘿,这可不是破布
叫他们抓紧这个
- 等我到那就打开它,好吗?
- 好的
Burt,小心
我爱你,Vicky
你怎么在这里?
回到谷仓去,快点
快去,走吧,快
请原谅
Joby,打开阀门
快
Joby,你知道这东西怎么弄吗?
- 转动手柄
- 什么?
转动手柄
按顶上的按钮
- 拿瓶子
- 好的
Joby!Joby!
回来
你会死的
Joby!
跑.快点,跑,Joby
瓶子在这儿!
扔啊.
是时候了
扔啊
Burt!
- Joby!
- Burt!
Joby!
- Vicky!Vicky!
- Sarah!
Joby!
看!看!
快点,快点,我们走
- 他死了吗?
- 我想是的
- 那我们为什么还跑?
- 总之继续跑
你在哪儿找到这小家伙的?
海明福特离这儿19英里,对吗?
我们走路去?
当然
Burt,你确定你有这个力气吗?
我没事
你呢?
你还好吧?
是的,我能行
我有个好医生
你最好相信
嫉妒?
那么我们拿这两个小家伙怎么办?
哦,我不知道
你们两个想跟我们在一起待几天吗?
一星期怎么样?
- 好吧
- 一个月怎样?
不
好吧好吧
我来找地图
你必须死
哦,她昏过去了
我们现在怎么做?
等到了西雅图给她寄张卡留念好了
让我们快点离开这儿